[{"answer": "Well, right now, what firefighters have done is they've sort of taken the upper hand at least on the northern flank of this fire.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "What's going on at the moment?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "With the firemen giving me excellent odds that they had pretty good control of things at the time, the answer would be yes.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "You stayed at your house all day, but when you left, did you think you were going to return to a house?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Scott Ochoa, city manager, O-C-H-O-A.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Can you spell your name please?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Let me go back to Kyung Lah now.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Can you come back, sir?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Did you think that you were ever going to be returning to a home yesterday?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "It's devastating.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "I mean, what kind of pit is that in your belly?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "I feel very fortunate today.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Anything you want to add, Paul?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, nobody's talking about it publicly, you know, but President Obama is literally getting asked about Syria every day, and again today, with this ratcheting up of tensions, the president once again said you know, no prospect that he can see of putting U.S. ground troops into Syria.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "What is likely to be the White House reaction to what's happened here?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Well, I think that the Israelis and all the countries in the region certainly would be prepared for that.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "And is it -- is the fear, Barbara, that the Syrians may respond in kind now against Israel?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "This will be national news.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "No, because she did what some are calling the apology tour.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Is this brand terminally damaging?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "DUI.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Arrested for what?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "You wouldn't listen to what he said to do and you kept getting out of the car.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What did I get arrested for?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, remember, she has been one of the biggest actresses in Hollywood since her early 20s.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Janice?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "So it's a very unique, interesting combination, you know what I mean?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Well, I didn't ask for anything.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "It's a smash hit around the world and you get zero dollars?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "But you can listen, you can whistle.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "What about the people like me that can neither write none of this nor dance?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "The greatest guitarist in the world.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I didn't come up with the title.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "How do you cope with that title?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "What I was trying to achieve is --", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Well, talking of Brad Paisley, this furor that erupted over \"Accidental Racist\", what were you trying to achieve?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "On top of that, there's plenty of white people that don't like me.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "You know, I hope -- you get what I'm saying?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "And music, too.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Love conquers all, you know?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Good genes and -- no, actually, just music.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "What is the art of survival?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "Could you still do that \"Jump\"?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "Hurts a little more when I land.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Same height?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Go to llcoolj.com.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "How do you get details for that?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "I'm doing well.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Are you holding up OK?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "I think the \"Today\" show is in comeback mode, just as it should be.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "What do you think is really going on now at the \"Today\" show?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Well, we heard Matt last night mentioned to Jay Leno that they talked sometime about each other's shows.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Have they known each other well, do you know?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "There's a lot to that.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "That if you're right there at the top, you're going to get gunned down?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "I'd like -- well, of course, I don't get paid nearly enough to answer this question.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "If you had been running NBC, would you have fired Ann Curry when they did?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "I thought David Carr's column was right on.", "docId": "130503pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "Were you right to be dissing out a few stones into glass houses, do you think?", "qSentId": 664}]